Tremble, right hand of mine...
By the contract we made, I order you
to shroud yourself in black flame
and grant my desire!
Now I can't heat up my chicken!
You sure about this?
Mayuri, this is no longer a microwave.
It's a time machine!
If you join the lab, you'll be dealing with this all day.
That's not fair!
Then go buy me a new microwave, Okarin.
I don't have the money.
I told you photographing me is prohibited.
It's to celebrate.
No photos!
Okay, done programming.
PhoneWave, 2nd edition, Version 1.03 is done.
Now you can use the
PhoneWave's cell phone
to send a D-Mail to any phone you like!
You did it, Daru!
Then let's continue our experiments.
Is it really a time machine?
Don't tell anyone, okay?
But don't you think the landlord
will get mad at us?
Part-time warrior!
Mayuri, be quiet!
Where's Mr. Braun?
Who's that?
Don't call my dad "Mr. Braun"...
You mean the boss? He's out on a service call.
I don't think he'll be back for a while.
Is that true?!
If it weren't, I wouldn't be screwing around outsi—
Mayuri.
Okay.
Tutturu
Received Mail
From: Mayuri
Subject: (None)
--   Mayushii
This is...
I saw a light.
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
Divergence
Singularity
Juicy Chicken Number 1 would taste better...
Hey, there's no Dr Pepper!
They were out.
If they're out, keep looking until you find some!
That's what it means to be a Dr Pepperian.
They didn't have any.
What do you want me to do about it?
You want some or not?
Geez...
What kind of mad scientist worries about
not getting enough vegetables?
Let's begin the Round Table.
It's hot in here. Let's open a window.
What are you doing, Daru?
What if the Organization discovers our secret...
Delusion fail!
What's a Round Table?
We will now move Operation Urd to stage two,
and take experiments on D-Mail
to a more practical level.
In the summer, you gotta have barley tea.
Want some too, Moeka?
Practical? What are we going to do?
Change the past.
Wait... That's too dangerous.
If you create a time paradox...
Assistant, as a scientist,
aren't you interested in whether we can
alter the past using D-Mail?
W-Well...
But what will we change?
Good question.
Here's what I want to accomplish
with this operation...
Win the lottery.
Okarin... Mayushii is very sad.
I'm in.
If I had money, I could buy
new parts for the computer,
and I could go to MayQueen all I want.
Don't you think we should work toward world peace?
Like give everyone in the world an Upa cushion...
Okabe, that's really lame.
It's an experiment to see
if we can change the past.
That would be the easiest way to tell!
But basically, you just want money, right?
Shut up, Celeb 17!
Cele... Huh?
Celeb 17!
I don't want to hear anything from a woman
living in a hotel on her parent's money!
I'm 18.
But there are all kinds of lottery tickets.
Which one do you want?
Well...
What's wrong?
No...
Where'd Moeka go?
Huh?
Wait!
Sheesh... I can't take my eyes
off you for a second.
It's because you didn't respond.
I really want to borrow
the IBN 5100. Please...
I'll take that as a yes?
Is she supposed to be a valley girl LOL?
Christina, keep a close eye on her,
so she doesn't wander around!
How am I supposed to do that?
Do you want to see the lab, Moeka?
I'll show you around later.
Mayushii is good at that!
I did it for Kurisu too!
Where should I start?
Aw, I see.
The LOTO SIX.
Every Thursday,
the winning numbers are announced.
We'll send the numbers to the past.
We're really doing this?
You have any other bright ideas?
Which division numbers do you want?
By the way, first division prize is...
two hundred million yen!
Two hundred million yen?
Wait, Daru.
Two hundred million yen is a bit much.
First division would draw too much attention.
The Organization is chasing me, after all.
You have cold feet, don't you?
What's second division?
Twenty-three million yen.
Third?
Seven hundred thousand.
We'll go with that!
Okabe's a chicken, isn't he?
That's coming from someone
worried about a time paradox, Celeb 17?
And this is the Upa cushion!
When you're tired or feeling down,
you give it a hug, like this!
And this is the fridge!
What's inside today?
Um...
Hey!
Shining Finger!
Here's your first mission as a lab mem.
Ooh, your first job!
Think of what to write in the D-Mail.
Something that'll make the me of
one week ago want to buy a LOTO SIX ticket.
Seven days ago
would be 168 hours,
so about 170 seconds on the timer should do it?
Buy LOTO SIX
You'll win!
Hm... That sounds about right.
Okay, we're ready.
At last, the time has come to open Steins Gate!
That again?
You really never tire of it, do you?
And you need to stop whining
about it every time.
You looked like you were having fun.
I-It's not like I'm having fun, all right?
That said, our assistant sure is a tsundere.
Who's a tsundere?!
Ooh, Miss Makise, you've heard of tsunderes?
I haven't!
No, you definitely responded like you did.
I said I haven't!
Okay, I'm starting up the microwave.
That's too dangerous.
If you create a time paradox...
Why am I so scared?
El Psy Kongroo!
Sending...
Sent
Okarin!
Are you okay?
Wh-What was that?
How long have I been standing here?
About 30 seconds, I guess.
Thirty seconds?
You don't remember?
We were just talking about an experiment
to see if we could change the past with a D-Mail.
Then...
You ran over to the PhoneWave
and started panting.
Mayushii, can you say "panting" again?
Stop it, pervert!
Buy LOTO SIX
It's here.
You'll win!
Okabe, are you really all right?
Where's the money?
The LOTO SIX!
Celeb Sev,  did I win third prize?
Don't call me Celeb Sev....
What are you talking about?
What do you mean? You...
Okarin?
The experiment?
We did an experiment to see if we could
change the past with the D-Mail...
We were just talking about what we could
do for the experiment.
Mayushii wants something
that'll bring about world peace!
Like giving everyone in the world an Upa cushion!
You really don't remember...
Come in!
It's Luka!
Welcome!
Kyouma, I'm sorry!
Luka?
This...
02, 12, 18...
It's the same.
Lukako! Where did you get this?
Um... You gave me the numbers.
I did?
You told me to buy it since it might win.
Wh-When?
One week ago.
Wow, Okarin's a psychic!
So, Luka, did you win?
Well... I got one of the numbers wrong.
So close!
Too close!
Okabe, did you use the PhoneWave to...
Hey, there's no Dr Pepper!
They didn't have any.
What do you want me to do about it?
There's no doubt that I sent the D-Mail,
but there's no record of it.
The past has been changed?
They didn't remember the experiment,
even though we all talked about it,
and we all observed.
Only I remember.
Only I...
This feeling! It's just like back then...
What's going on?
What's that?
Something important.
What's wrong?
You look like you've been brainwashed.
Brainwashed...
It's possible.
But was I the one brainwashed... or were they?
What?
There's no chip.
It's okay.
You're not brainwashed.
Chip?
What's "brainwashed"?
That's...
I, Hououin Kyouma, will tell you.
I guess Nae's scared of Okabe Rintaro.
There's something I want to ask you.
Electricity?
You mean when there are all those sparks?
You did it before, didn't you?
There should've been one 10 minutes ago.
I didn't notice that one.
What about you, Nae?
Nope!
You really are a pervert!
I'm not a pervert!
I'm a pervert-gentleman!
See?
I told you that you can hear it.
I didn't know it was this bad...
Did you hear about the time machine?
Yeah. Nice job, I guess!
Let me warn you...
I know... I won't tell anyone.
Are you worried about something
related to the time machine?
Then why not ask John Titor?
Come to think of it,
John Titor mentioned this.
If you go to the past and change it,
this alters something called
the divergence number,
and the worldline moves to another world.
When there's a worldline shift,
people's memories are altered,
and memories of the new world are created.
The D-Mail moved the worldline
from a world where Lukako
didn't buy the LOTO SIX ticket
to one where he did.
The worldline changed, and so did the past.
In this world,
I didn't send the D-Mail
with the winning LOTO SIX number
into the past.
It's not that the other lab mems
don't remember the experiment.
It never happened.
So why am I the only one who remembers?
Oh, no!
Nae, whatever he asks,
don't tell him I was slacking off!
Will you give me a ride on your bike?
I will!
Okabe Rintaro!
I'm on your side, okay?
You!
Daddy!
Okabe!
What were you doing with my daughter?!
W-Wait! I wasn't doing anything!
Shut up!
A guy like you wouldn't be able to control his desires if left alone with my adorable daughter!
Do you always think about me like that?
And we weren't alone...
Suzuha was just here too.
What? Is that true, Nae?
I promised, so I can't say she was slacking off.
What?
Hey! Part-timer!
Knock on wood!
You were slacking off!
Argh, you left the 42-inch on!
I-I'm sorry!
I'll explain why later.
We're stopping the experiment for today.
We're done for the day.
Okarin...
So, little miss assistant there, you're not going home?
I'm just thinking about something.
I see.
You'd be all alone if you went back to the hotel,
so you want me to spend time with you.
Right, little Celeb Sev?
Don't call me Celeb Sev!
I've gotta send this text message.
If you want to stay here, be quiet, The Zombie.
That's the name that bugs me the most.
You're like a girl,
waiting for a message from her crush.
You really want attention that much?
Who was that message for?
John Titor.
Lukako
The Lottery
I'm really sorry
I Had Fun
Next time, tell me about
the time machine.
It's a promise.
A promise, right?
Bye!
Moeka
Daru?
Hello.
Okarin, I realized I made a huge mistake!
A mistake? What?
Actually... Actually...
I left my wallet at the lab!
What?
So now I can't get into MayQueen!
Okarin, would you...
Okarin!
Oh, it's you Mayuri.
Daru's with you, right?
You don't need to lend him money, okay?
Got it.
So, Okarin, do you feel better?
If you don't, you can hug Mayushii's Upa, okay?
Then you'll feel better.
Okay.
I'm hanging up.
Good luck at work.
Thanks.
Bye!
Okabe, you're smiling.
It's here!
I read your message.
Just as you deduced,
the past was changed, and the worldline has undoubtedly moved.
The one thing I don't understand
is why you retain your memories
from before the change.
Is that true?
It's true.
Something similar happened before.
What does this mean?
I don't know.
The concept of changing the past
via email was never considered,
even in the year 2036.
You changed the past and moved worldlines.
But it's never been confirmed if
anyone alive can maintain their memories
over a worldline jump and observe the change.
But...
Kyouma, you may have that power.
You may be able to lead the world
beyond Divergence 1%...
Lead the world?
What lies beyond Divergence 1%?
What happens then?
Sending...
Sent
What lies beyond it is true freedom.
If you can't cross that barrier,
the future will become a dystopia.
My goal is to change the future.
And you may be the one who has that power.
Okabe, what's wrong?
What's he talking about?
Me? Change the future?
That's...
Kyouma,
I want...
...you to be the messiah.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
ansoku no asu wo negattara
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
habatake butterfly
Spread your wings
kiseki no butterfly
butterfly of miracles
anata he sasageru
I dedicate it to you
namida no butterfly
Oh butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
butterfly of radiance
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
everything will now be rewritten